You're not getting away!
It's tiny...
and hard to target!
All right! I can do it!
FEAR
EPISODE 7:
AWFUL VILLAIN
What a horrible voice!
My ears!
But...
I can do it!
I can behead it!
HATRED
What's this?
Behind me...
There's something behind me!
Joy!
Anger!
Sorrow!
Pleasure!
This doesn't smell like any other demon!
What's behind me?
What should I do?
I'm just going to focus
on slashing its head off!
If I can just behead it, I'm sure—
Too hard!
I can't slash any farther!
The power from Nezuko's blood
has run out, too!
Tanjiro! Get out of the way!
It's no good!
That was the wrong call!
Genya can't fire his gun...
without hitting me, as well!
Oh, crap!
HATRED
Here comes an attack!
DESTROY
Nezuko!
Are you okay?
She'll be fine!
Her arms and legs have regenerated!
You brutal fiends who torment the weak...
Atrocious...
Offensive...
to the extreme.
UPPER FOUR
Damn you, awful villains...
A sixth...
demon?
Another one showed up?
Come on, enough is enough!
No.
That's not the sixth one.
The four Emotions.
There's no trace of the other demons!
What the hell is this?
What's going on here?
That one was the Anger Demon
just a second ago!
The moment Tanjiro's sword
nearly slashed that tiny demon's neck...
the Anger Demon raised both hands!
And in the blink of an eye,
he drew in...
the Joy Demon and the Pleasure Demon!
UPPER FOUR
He pulverized their flesh...
then absorbed both demons!
Then, in another instant...
the Anger Demon moved toward Aizetsu!
UPPER
FOUR
Aizetsu opened his mouth as if to protest...
but he was absorbed
before he could get a word out!
The Anger Demon's body transformed...
and turned into that!
What's up with that?
He absorbed those three demons?
Did he fuse with them?
This wasn't a split,
but he got even younger!
He's a kid!
He's surpassed the probable main body,
the old geezer...
and fused!
Oh, crap!
The main body's being surrounded!
Hold up!
I can't breathe!
It's so overpowering!
My heart hurts!
What is it?
You wretch...
Do you have a problem
with what I'm doing?
Well...
you...
awful villains?
So heavy!
That voice!
That force!
It's sapping the strength from my limbs!
I can't stay on my feet!
What makes...
What makes us...
awful villains?
It's because you torment the weak.
Right?
Just now, you tried to slash a small, weak being
who could fit in the palm of your hand.
Utterly atrocious!
Only a pure fiend would do that!
Small, weak being?
Who...
Who's small and weak?
Don't give me that!
That scent you're giving off...
The scent of blood...
It's not just 100 or even 200 humans
that you've devoured!
What did those people ever do to you?
Did they all do something
they had to pay for with their lives?
Don't you dare play the victim card
after killing and eating scores of people!
You're twisted through and through!
You won't get away with this!
You evil demon...
I'll be the one to behead you!
DEMON SLAYER: KIMETSU NO YAIBA
SWORDSMITH VILLAGE ARC
That demon...
How can it be so overpowering?
I can't move a muscle!
Is that all you have to say?
I'm going to...
cut your head off!
Were any of the humans I devoured
members of your family?
No.
Then, it has nothing to do with you.
That's not what I'm talking about!
People like that...
people who will suffer
the same way after this...
I'm not letting any more go through that!
Surely, you have nothing to do
with those people, either.
What kind of reason
does one person need to help another?
If you can't understand something like that,
then you're the fiend!
Hyo, hyo, hyo!
UPPER FIVE
That look of fake stoicism...
How very sublime it is!
My creative juices are simply gushing!
Not that I wouldn't love to stay
and watch you die in there a bit longer...
but first, I'll be taking a look
inside this shack.
Now, what on earth could they
be protecting so fiercely here?
Hyo, hyo, hyo!
With the air left in my lungs...
I can just manage one more attack!
Mist Breathing...
First Form...
Low Clouds Distance Haze!
I can't break through
even with this thrust attack.
It's no wonder,
given how badly chipped this sword is.
It's futile.
It's over.
I hope that help is on the way.
Master...
I'm going to die...
so please send...
at least two Hashira.
What makes you think that?
Nobody knows what the future holds.
What's that?
No, wait.
Tanjiro never...
said such a thing to me.
So, who...
did say it?
No, you don't!
I won't let you inside!
Hyo, hyo!
Why do you even bother?
Could it be that you actually think
you can fend me off somehow?
Hyo, hyo, hyo!
Well, that's...
comical!
What good will it do you
to frantically defend this sorry shack?
The village chief
wouldn't be here, right?
Hmm?
Extraordinary steel!
What an extraordinary sword!
That human is young.
The body of someone not yet 40.
Surely he's not the chief.
Such brilliant craftsmanship!
It's stunning!
Hmm...
Hey, you human there!
Who is the creator?
By what kind of person
was this sword forged?
Why did he carve this single character
rather than his own name?
No!
I understand!
I understand why!
Damn him!
What kind of focus is that?
He's so immersed that he's unaware of me!
I...
I don't like this!
Even I've never concentrated this hard!
As an artist, I feel inferior!
Hyo!
Stop it!
Mr. Haganezuka!
M-Mr. Haganezuka...
What the...
Th-That man still refuses to stop!
The reason why he didn't carve his name
into such an incredible sword...
This single character!
This sword was forged with nothing
but single-minded determination!
This sword...
was forged for this sole purpose
and nothing else!
Mr. Haganezuka!
I don't like this!
It would be child's play to kill him,
but I want to somehow make this man
abandon that sword!
I want to shatter his concentration!
My vision...
is getting distorted.
I'm dying.
I'm out of air.
You can't decide for yourself
when it's all over.
You never told me that.
I promise you, it will be all right.
Don't give up.
Someone will save you for sure.
Come on.
So, I have to leave it to someone else?
That's the worst thing I could do.
This is about all anyone can do on their own.
That's why people join forces
and work together.
There's no one who can save me...
because everyone's weaker than I am.
I'm the one
who should've been stronger.
But I misjudged myself.
I overestimated my own skills...
subconsciously...
because I'm a Hashira.
You're not wrong, Muichiro.
You'll be fine.
I'm going to die
because I made more than one mistake.
Mr. Tokito!
I won't let you die!
Mr. Tokito, hang in there!
HYOTTOKO
I'll get you out, no matter what!
I'm going to save you!
Crap! What is this?
It's all rubbery and disgusting!
If even I can't slash through it,
how on earth can you?
You have bigger priorities
than me right now.
Protect the chief.
Oh, that would be beyond you.
At least make a run for it
with as many swords as you can hold.
What are you doing? Behind you!
Hello!
Behind you!
Blood!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Just run!
Hurry the hell up!
His solar plexus.
He got stabbed in a vital point.
He's going to die.
You're not strong enough!
Why don't you get it?
Put pressure on that wound!
Get the hell out of here!
Stay away from me!
Don't try to save me!
There's nothing you can do!
Whatever you do for others
comes around to help you, as well, in the end.
And humans are creatures...
who can summon unbelievable strength...
for the sake of someone
other than themselves...
Muichiro.
Yes, I know.
Mist Breathing, Second Form...
Eight-Layered Mist!
I remember now, Tanjiro.
My father...
had the same...
red eyes as you!
PART 7
30 KG
So, this is what you've been up to in secret?
But why should you have to go this far?
The swordsman puts his life
on the line in battle...
so his swordsmith should feel
even more pressure...
as he pours his soul into his sword!
Oh yeah?
Now, it's time for a Taisho-era secret!
The knife he was wielding
when he chased after Mr. Tanjiro...
was forged by Mr. Haganezuka himself...
but since it's unbelievably sharp,
he says he's too scared
to use it for cooking!
Is that totally pointless or what?
Mr. Haganezuka?
Scary, scary, scary!
Mr. Haganezuka,
you're scaring me! So scary!
Next, Episode 8, "The Mu in Muichiro"!
TO BE CONTINUED